International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records on Microfilm 5432 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1937: Reel no.3 (Reel 85)
  - Locals - Bogota, 1937; 3 (Reel 85)
  - Locals - Dalhousie, 1937; 4 (Reel 85)
  - Locals - Eau Claire, 1937; 5 (Reel 85)
- 1937: Reel no.4 (Reel 86)
  - Local Unions - Edmunston, 1937; 1 (Reel 86)
  - Local Unions - Green Bay, 1937; 2 (Reel 86)
  - Local Unions-Iroquois Falls, 1937; 3 (Reel 86)
  - Local Unions-Luke, 1937; 4 (Reel 86)
  - Local Unions-Middletown, 1937; 5 (Reel 86)
- 1937: Reel no.5 (Reel 87)
  - Locals-Millinocket, 1937; 1 (Reel 87)
  - Locals-Oakland, 1937; 2 (Reel 87)
  - Locals-Port Angeles, 1937; 3 (Reel 87)
  - Locals- Riverside, 1937; 4 (Reel 87)
  - Locals-San Francisco, 1937; 5 (Reel 87)
- 1937: Reel no.6 (Reel 88)
  - Locals-Sartell, 1937; 1 (Reel 88)
  - Locals-Toledo, 1937; 2 (Reel 88)
  - Locals-York, 1937; 3 (Reel 88)
  - Unions - D'Aoust, J., 1937; 4 (Reel 88)
  - Unions-A. F. of L., 1937; 5 (Reel 88)
- 1937: Reel no.7 (Reel 89)
  - Unions-A. F. of L., 1937; 1 (Reel 89)
  - General Files A-Z-Miscellaneous, 1937; 2 (Reel 89)
  - Companies-Booth, J. R., 1937; 3 (Reel 89)
  - Company Associations, 1937; 4 (Reel 89)
- 1938: Reel no.1 (Reel 90)
  - President Secretary Files, 1938; 1 (Reel 90)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1938; 2 (Reel 90)
  - Officers-Doody, Bat, 1938; 3 (Reel 90)
  - Officers-Taylor, J, W., 1938; 4 (Reel 90)
  - Organizers-Barnes, F. C., 1938; 5 (Reel 90)
- 1938: Reel no.2 (Reel 91)
  - Organizers-Beach, H., 1938; 1 (Reel 91)
  - Organizers-Killen, J., 1938; 2 (Reel 91)
  - Organizers - Louy, L.J., 1938; 3 (Reel 91)
  - Organizers - Stephan, J., 1938; 4 (Reel 91)
- 1938: Reel no.3 (Reel 92)
  - Organizers - Trautman, W., 1938; 1 (Reel 92)
  - Organizers - Reynolds, L.C., 1938; 2 (Reel 92)
  - Locals - Beaupre, 1938; 3 (Reel 92)
  - Locals - Cloquet, 1938; 4 (Reel 92)
  - Locals - Coshocton, 1938; 5 (Reel 92)
- 1938: Reel no.4 (Reel 93)
  - Locals-Covington, 1938; 1 (Reel 93)
  - Locals-Espanola, 1938; 2 (Reel 93)
  - Locals-Grand Rapids, 1938; 3 (Reel 93)
  - Locals 0 Herrings, 1938; 4 (Reel 93)
  - Locals - Iroquois Falls, 1938; 5 (Reel 93)
- 1938: Reel no.5 (Reel 94)
  - Local Unions-Jaite, 1938; 1 (Reel 94)
  - Local Unions-Luke, 1938; 2 (Reel 94)
  - Local Unions-Minneapolis, 1938; 3 (Reel 94)
  - Local Unions-Owen, 1938; 4 (Reel 94)
  - Local Unions-Port Angeles, 1938; 5 (Reel 94)
- 1938: Reel no.6 (Reel 95)
  - Locals-Port Arthur, 1938; 1 (Reel 95)
  - Locals-St. Helens, 1938; 2 (Reel 95)
  - Locals-Tacoma, 1938; 3 (Reel 95)
  - Locals - Watertown, 1938; 4 (Reel 95)
  - Unions - Ottawa H & G. Paper Mills Unions, 1938; 5 (Reel 95)
- 1938: Reel no.7 (Reel 96)
  - Pacific Coast P. & Paper Mill Employees Association, 1938; 1 (Reel 96)
  - Unions-D'Oust, J. A, 1938; 2 (Reel 96)
  - Misc.-Comm. for T. Mooney, 1938; 3 (Reel 96)
  - Companies - Hoberg Paper Co., 1938; 4 (Reel 96)
  - Company Associations, 1938; 5 (Reel 96)
- 1939: Reel no.1 (Reel 97)
  - President Secretary Files, 1939; 1 (Reel 97)
  - Officers-Doody, Pat, 1939; 2 (Reel 97)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1939; 3 (Reel 97)
  - Officers-Executive Board, 1939; 4 (Reel 97)
  - Organizers-Goodman, H., 1939; 5 (Reel 97)
- 1939: Reel no.2 (Reel 98)
  - Organizers-Gordon, L., 1939; 1 (Reel 98)
  - Organizers-Killen, J.J., 1939; 2 (Reel 98)
  - Organizers-Mangam, E. A., 1939; 3 (Reel 98)
  - Organizers-Trautman, W., 1939; 4 (Reel 98)
  - Organizers-Trautman, W., 1939; 5 (Reel 98)
- 1939: Reel no.3 (Reel 99)
  - Organizers-Weissfield, F., 1939; 1 (Reel 99)
  - Organizers-Smith, W, M., 1939; 2 (Reel 99)
  - Locals-Akron, 1939; 3 (Reel 99)
  - Locals-Carthage, 1939; 4 (Reel 99)
  - Locals-Covington, 1939; 5 (Reel 99)
- 1939: Reel no.4 (Reel 100)
  - Locals-Dalhousie, 1939; 1 (Reel 100)
  - Locals-Franklin, 1939; 2 (Reel 100)
  - Locals-Hoquiam, 1939; 3 (Reel 100)
  - Locals - Louisiana, 1939; 4 (Reel 100)
  - Locals-Milwaukee, 1939; 5 (Reel 100)
- 1939: Reel no.5 (Reel 101)
  - Locals-Milwaukee, 1939; 1 (Reel 101)
  - Locals - Oswego, 1939; 2 (Reel 101)
  - Locals-Port Mellon, 1939; 3 (Reel 101)
  - Locals-St. Helens, 1939; 4 (Reel 101)
  - Locals-South Prewer, 1939; 5 (Reel 101)
- 1939: Reel no.6 (Reel 102)
  - Locals Unions-South Gate, 1939; 1 (Reel 102)
  - Local Unions-Vancouver, 1939; 2 (Reel 102)
  - Unions-Quebec Prov. Council of Paper Mill, 1939; 3 (Reel 102)
  - Unions - Mathew J. Burns, 1939; 4 (Reel 102)
  - Int. Unions - Int. Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1939; 5 (Reel 102)
- 1939: Reel no.7 (Reel 103)
  - Int. Union - Int. Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1939; 1 (Reel 103)
  - Federations - Trade & Labor Congress of Canada, 1939; 2 (Reel 103)
  - Misc. - General Files A-Z, 1939; 3 (Reel 103)
  - Companies - A.P.W. Paper Co., 1939; 4 (Reel 103)
  - Company Associations, 1939; 5 (Reel 103)
- 1940: Reel no.1 (Reel 104)
  - President Secretary Files, 1940; 1 (Reel 104)
  - Officers-Burnell, Wm., 1940; 2 (Reel 104)
  - Officer-Richards, R.A., 1940; 3 (Reel 104)
  - Officers-Sullivan, H. W, 1940; 4 (Reel 104)
  - Organizers-Anderson, R., 1940; 5 (Reel 104)
- 1940: Reel no.2 (Reel 105)
  - Organizers - Barnes, F.C., 1940; 1 (Reel 105)
  - Organizers - Hineline, Wm., 1940; 2 (Reel 105)
  - Organizers-Humble, H., 1940; 3 (Reel 105)
  - Organizers - Mangam, E.A., 1940; 4 (Reel 105)
  - Organizers - Stephen, J., 1940; 5 (Reel 105)
- 1940: Reel no.3 (Reel 106)
  - Organizers - Taylor, E., 1940; 1 (Reel 106)
  - Organizers - Malin, J.H., 1940; 2 (Reel 106)
  - Circular Letters, 1940; 3 (Reel 106)
  - Local Unions-Carthage, 1940; 4 (Reel 106)
  - Local Unions-Cloquet, 1940; 5 (Reel 106)
- 1940: Reel no.4 (Reel 107)
  - Locals - Cohoes, 1940; 1 (Reel 107)
  - Locals-Edmunston, 1940; 2 (Reel 107)
  - Locals-Fort Francis, 1940; 3 (Reel 107)
  - Locals-Jacksonville, 1940; 4 (Reel 107)
  - Locals-Lowell, 1940; 5 (Reel 107)
- 1940: Reel no.5 (Reel 108)
  - Locals-Lufkin, 1940; 1 (Reel 108)
  - Locals-Milwaukee, 1940; 2 (Reel 108)
  - Locals-Natural Dam, 1940; 3 (Reel 108)
  - Locals-Owen, 1940; 4 (Reel 108)
  - Locals-Pittsburg, 1940; 5 (Reel 108)
- 1940: Reel no.6 (Reel 109)
  - Local Unions-Plattsburg, 1940; 1 (Reel 109)
  - Local Unions-Salem, 1940; 2 (Reel 109)
  - Local Unions-Smooth Rock Falls, 1940; 3 (Reel 109)
  - Local Unions-Waygamack, 1940; 4 (Reel 109)
  - Unions-Dist. Council of Paper Mill Unions, 1940; 5 (Reel 109)
- 1940: Reel no.7 (Reel 110)
  - Unions-Pacific Coast Employee's Assoc., 1940; 1 (Reel 110)
  - Unions - Phillips, P.L., 1940; 2 (Reel 110)
  - Unions - Appleton Trades & Labor Council, 1940; 3 (Reel 110)
  - Government - Social Security, 1940; 4 (Reel 110)
  - Company Associations, 1940; 5 (Reel 110)
- 1941: Reel no.1 (Reel 111)
  - President Secretary Files, 1941; 1 (Reel 111)
  - Officers-Doody, Bat, 1941; 2 (Reel 111)
  - Officers-Richards, R. A., 1941; 3 (Reel 111)
  - Officers-Stephens, S. A., 1941; 4 (Reel 111)
  - Organizers - 1941, 5 (Reel 111)
- 1941: Reel no.2 (Reel 112)
  - Organizers - Anderson, R., 1941; 1 (Reel 112)
  - Organizers - Rever, M., 1941; 2 (Reel 112)
  - Organizers - Hineline, Wm., 1941; 3 (Reel 112)
  - Organizers - Isaacson, I.D., 1941; 4 (Reel 112)
  - Organizers - Leon, Raymond, 1941; 5 (Reel 112)
- 1941: Reel no.3 (Reel 113)
  - Organizers - Louy, L.J., 1941; 1 (Reel 113)
  - Organizers - Ruddick, G., 1941; 2 (Reel 113)
  - Organizers - Van Deusen, F., 1941; 3 (Reel 113)
  - Special Organizers - Stewart, L.E., 1941; 4 (Reel 113)
  - Local Unions-Akron, 1941; 5 (Reel 113)
- 1941: Reel no.4 (Reel 114)
  - Local Unions-Alden, 1941; 1 (Reel 114)
  - Local Unions-Carthage, 1941; 2 (Reel 114)
  - Local Unions-Cornwall, 1941; 3 (Reel 114)
  - Local Unions-Ft. Clinch, 1941; 4 (Reel 114)
  - Local Unions-Gatineau, 1941; 5 (Reel 114)
- 1941: Reel no.5 (Reel 115)
  - Local Unions-Georgetown, 1941; 1 (Reel 115)
  - Local Unions-Jacksonville, 1941; 2 (Reel 115)
  - Local Unions-Menasha, 1941; 3 (Reel 115)
  - Local Unions-Mobile, 1941; 4 (Reel 115)
  - Local Unions-Mt. Carmel, 1941; 5 (Reel 115)
- 1941: Reel no.6 (Reel 116)
  - Local Unions-Munising, 1941; 1 (Reel 116)
  - Local Unions-Owen, 1941; 2 (Reel 116)
  - Local Unions-Paper Tubes & Specialties, 1941; 3 (Reel 116)
  - Local Unions-Quebec, 1941; 4 (Reel 116)
  - Local Unions-Rumford, Mexico, 1941; 5 (Reel 116)
- 1941: Reel no.7 (Reel 117)
  - Local Unions-St. Helens, 1941; 1 (Reel 117)
  - Local Unions-Shelbyville, 1941; 2 (Reel 117)
  - Local Unions-Thunder Bay, 1941; 3 (Reel 117)
  - Unions-Northem N.Y. Paper Mill Workers, 1941; 4 (Reel 117)
  - Unions-Carpenters & Joiners, 1941; 5 (Reel 117)
- 1941: Reel no.8 (Reel 118)
  - Unions-Electrical Workers, 1941; 1 (Reel 118)
  - Unions-Photo Engravers, 1941; 2 (Reel 118)
  - Unions-Woll, V, 1941; 3 (Reel 118)
  - Unions-Three Rivers Labor Council, 1941; 4 (Reel 118)
  - Government-United States, 1941; 5 (Reel 118)
- 1941: Reel no.9 (Reel 119)
  - Government-United States, 1941; 1 (Reel 119)
  - Conv.-General Files, 1941; 2 (Reel 119)
  - Misc.-General Files, 1941; 3 (Reel 119)
  - Companies-Halifax Power & Pulp Co., 1941; 4 (Reel 119)
  - Companies-Keystone Box Co, 1941; 5 (Reel 119)
- 1941: Reel no.10 (Reel 120)
  - Companies-Kieckhefer Cont. Co., 1941; 1 (Reel 120)
  - Companies-St. Regis Paper Co., 1941; 2 (Reel 120)
  - Company Associations, 1941; 3 (Reel 120)
- 1942: Reel no.1 (Reel 121)
  - President-Secretary Files, 1942; 1 (Reel 121)
  - Officers-Doody, Bat, 1942; 2 (Reel 121)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1942; 3 (Reel 121)
  - Executive Board, 1942; 4 (Reel 121)
  - Organizers - Anderson, W., 1942; 5 (Reel 121)
- 1942: Reel no.2 (Reel 122)
  - Organizers-Barnes, F.., 1942; 1 (Reel 122)
  - Organizers - Goodman, H., 1942; 2 (Reel 122)
  - Organizers-Isaacson, I. D., 1942; 3 (Reel 122)
  - Organizers-Louy, L. J., 1942; 4 (Reel 122)
  - Organizers, - Louy, H., 1942; 5 (Reel 122)
- 1942: Reel no.3 (Reel 123)
  - Organizers - Mangam, E.A., 1942; 1 (Reel 123)
  - Organizers - Taylor, E., 1942; 2 (Reel 123)
  - Organizers - Wray, M., 1942; 3 (Reel 123)
  - Organizers - Ohlsen, M.P., 1942; 4 (Reel 123)
  - Circular letters, 1942; 5 (Reel 123)
- 1942: Reel no.4 (Reel 124)
  - Circular Letters Cont., 1942; 1 (Reel 124)
  - Local Unions-Carnegie, 1942; 2 (Reel 124)
  - Local Unions-Continental, 1942; 3 (Reel 124)
  - Local Union - Fort William, 1942; 4 (Reel 124)
  - Local Unions - Fulton, Oswego Falls, 1942; 5 (Reel 124)
- 1942: Reel no.5 (Reel 125)
  - Local Unions-Garden City, 1942; 1 (Reel 125)
  - Local Unions-Jacksonville, 1942; 2 (Reel 125)
  - Local Unions-Liverpool, 1942; 3 (Reel 125)
  - Local Unions - Milwaukee, 1942; 4 (Reel 125)
- 1942: Reel no.6 (Reel 126)
  - Local Unions-Milwaukee Cont., 1942; 1 (Reel 126)
  - Local Unions-Owen, 1942; 2 (Reel 126)
  - Local Unions-Pittsburg, 1942; 3 (Reel 126)
  - Local Unions-Sartell, 1942; 4 (Reel 126)
  - Local Unions-Temiskaming, 1942; 5 (Reel 126)
- 1942: Reel no.7 (Reel 127)
  - Local Unions-Terminal, 1942; 1 (Reel 127)
  - Local Unions-Wausau, 1942; 2 (Reel 127)
  - Local Unions-Federal Employees, 1942; 3 (Reel 127)
  - Federations - A.F. of L., 1942; 4 (Reel 127)
  - Federations - Wisconsin, 1942; 5 (Reel 127)
- 1942: Reel no.8 (Reel 128)
  - Other Organizations, 1942; 1 (Reel 128)
  - Government-United States, 1942; 2 (Reel 128)
  - Misc-Generel Files A-Z, 1942; 3 (Reel 128)
  - Companies - Cohoes Envelope Co., 1942; 4 (Reel 128)
  - Companies-N. Caroline Pulp Co., 1942; 5 (Reel 128)
- 1942: Reel no.9 (Reel 129)
  - Companies-Northern Kraft Corp., 1942; 1 (Reel 129)
  - Companies-Powell River Co., 1942; 2 (Reel 129)
  - Company Associations, 1942; 3 (Reel 129)
- 1943: Reel no.1 (Reel 130)
  - President Secretary Files, 1943; 1 (Reel 130)
  - Officers - Doody, Bat, 1943; 2 (Reel 130)
  - Officers - Richards, R.A., 1943; 3 (Reel 130)
  - Officers-Stephans, S.A., 1943; 4 (Reel 130)
  - Officers - Sullivan, H.W., 1943; 5 (Reel 130)
- 1943: Reel no.2 (Reel 131)
  - Executive Board, 1943; 1 (Reel 131)
  - Organizers - Beaver, M., 1943; 2 (Reel 131)
  - Organizers - Hansen, H.L., 1943; 3 (Reel 131)
  - Organizers - Killen, J.S., 1943; 4 (Reel 131)
  - Organizers - Louy, L., 1943; 5 (Reel 131)
- 1943: Reel no.3 (Reel 132)
  - Organizers - Manga, E. A., 1943; 1 (Reel 132)
  - Organizers - Stephen, J., 1943; 2 (Reel 132)
  - Organizers - Tonelli, J., 1943; 3 (Reel 132)
  - Organizers - Jordan, C., 1943; 4 (Reel 132)
  - Special Organizers - Wiedenbeck, E., 1943; 5 (Reel 132)
- 1943: Reel no.4 (Reel 133)
  - Conference Reports, 1943; 1 (Reel 133)
  - Local Unions - Bathurst, 1943; 2 (Reel 133)
  - Local Unions - Carnegie, 1943; 3 (Reel 133)
  - Local Unions - Erie, 1943; 4 (Reel 133)
  - Local Unions-Fort Orange, 1943; 5 (Reel 133)
- 1943: Reel no.5 (Reel 134)
  - Local Unions-Fort William, 1943; 1 (Reel 134)
  - Local Unions-Hull, 1943; 2 (Reel 134)
  - Local Unions - Kenora, 1943; 3 (Reel 134)
  - Local Unions - Manistique, 1943; 4 (Reel 134)
  - Local Unions - Merritton, 1943; 5 (Reel 134)
- 1943: Reel no.6 (Reel 135)
  - Local Unions - Messalonskee, 1943; 1 (Reel 135)
  - Local Unions-Paper Box Makers of greater N.Y., 1943; 3 (Reel 135)
  - Local Unions-Nekocsa-Edwards, 1943; 2 (Reel 135)
  - Local Unions - Reading, 1943; 4 (Reel 135)
  - Local Unions - Saut Ste. Marie, 1943; 5 (Reel 135)
- 1943: Reel no.7 (Reel 136)
  - Local Unions-Savannah, 1943; 1 (Reel 136)
  - Local Unions-Toledo, 1943; 2 (Reel 136)
  - Local Unions - Webster, 1943; 3 (Reel 136)
  - Int. Unions - Jones, J.R., 1943; 4 (Reel 136)
  - Int. Unions - Woll, M., 1943; 5 (Reel 136)
- 1943: Reel no.8 (Reel 137)
  - Int. Unions - Arkansas State Fed. of Lab., 1943; 1 (Reel 137)
  - Governments-United States, 1943; 2 (Reel 137)
  - Governments-United States, 1943; 3 (Reel 137)
  - Misc.- General Files, 1943; 4 (Reel 137)
  - Mics. - General Files, 1943; 5 (Reel 137)
- 1943: Reel no.9 (Reel 138)
  - General-General Files, 1943; 1 (Reel 138)
  - Companies-Crown Zellerback Corp., 1943; 2 (Reel 138)
  - Companies-Minn. & Ontario Paper Co., 1943; 3 (Reel 138)
  - Company Associations, 1943; 4 (Reel 138)
- 1944: Reel no.1 (Reel 139)
  - President Secretary Filer, 1944; 1 (Reel 139)
  - Officers- Doody, Bat, 1944; 2 (Reel 139)
  - Officers- Morris, F., 1944; 3 (Reel 139)
  - Officers- Richards, R. A., 1944; 4 (Reel 139)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1944; 5 (Reel 139)
- 1944: Reel no.2 (Reel 140)
  - Officers-Stephens, S.A., 1944; 1 (Reel 140)
  - Officers - Sullivan, H.W., 1944; 2 (Reel 140)
  - Organizers - Aubut, B., 1944; 3 (Reel 140)
  - Organizers - Hoff, A.B., 1944; 4 (Reel 140)
  - Organizers - Hoff, A.B., 1944; 5 (Reel 140)
- 1944: Reel no.3 (Reel 141)
  - Organizers - Isaacson, I.D., 1944; 1 (Reel 141)
  - Organizers - Mangan, E.A., 1944; 2 (Reel 141)
  - Organizers - Riggs, W.E., 1944; 3 (Reel 141)
  - Organizers - Stephen, J., 1944; 4 (Reel 141)
  - Organizers - Taylor, F., 1944; 5 (Reel 141)
- 1944: Reel no.4 (Reel 142)
  - Organizers-Van Deusen, F, C., 1944; 1 (Reel 142)
  - Organizers - Wetherbec, L., 1944; 2 (Reel 142)
  - Locals-Beaver Wood Fibre, 1944; 3 (Reel 142)
  - Locals - Cornwall, 1944; 4 (Reel 142)
  - Locals-Dexter, 1944; 5 (Reel 142)
- 1944: Reel no.5 (Reel 143)
  - Locals - Dominion, 1944; 1 (Reel 143)
  - Locals - Grand Rapids, 1944; 2 (Reel 143)
  - Locals-Kaukauna, 1944; 3 (Reel 143)
  - Locals - Luke, 1944; 4 (Reel 143)
  - Locals - Miami Valley, 1944; 5 (Reel 143)
- 1944: Reel no.6 (Reel 144)
  - Locals - Middletown, 1944; 1 (Reel 144)
  - Locals- New Bedford, 1944; 2 (Reel 144)
  - Locals - Paper Tubes & Specialties, 1944; 3 (Reel 144)
  - Locals - Presswood, 1944; 4 (Reel 144)
  - Locals - St. Albans, 1944; 5 (Reel 144)
- 1944: Reel no.7 (Reel 145)
  - Locals-St. Helens, 1944; 1 (Reel 145)
  - Locals-Star, 1944; 2 (Reel 145)
  - Locale-Woodfibre, 1944; 3 (Reel 145)
  - Unions-Glove Workers, 1944; 4 (Reel 145)
  - Local Unions-Paper Makers, 1944; 5 (Reel 145)
- 1944: Reel no.8 (Reel 146)
  - Unions-Paper Makers, 1944; 1 (Reel 146)
  - Unions-Newfoundland F. of L., 1944; 2 (Reel 146)
  - Governments-United States, 1944; 3 (Reel 146)
  - Governments-United States, 1944; 4 (Reel 146)
  - General Files-Burke, J. P., 1944; 5 (Reel 146)
- 1944: Reel no.9 (Reel 147)
  - General Files-Conventions, 1944; 1 (Reel 147)
  - General Files -Letters from Boys, 1944; 2 (Reel 147)
  - Companies- Abitibi Power & Paper Co., 1944; 3 (Reel 147)
  - Companies-Mosinee Paper Mills Co., 1944; 4 (Reel 147)
  - Company Associations, 1944; 5 (Reel 147)
- 1945: Reel no.1 (Reel 148)
  - President Secretary Files, 1945; 1 (Reel 148)
  - Officers - Burnell, W.H., 1945; 2 (Reel 148)
  - Officers-Lacroix, L. P., 1945; 3 (Reel 148)
  - Officers-Richards, R. A., 1945; 4 (Reel 148)
  - Officers-Richards, R. A., 1945; 5 (Reel 148)
- 1945: Reel no.2 (Reel 149)
  - Officers - Sherman, J., 1945; 1 (Reel 149)
  - Officers - Stephens, S.A., 1945; 2 (Reel 149)
  - Officers - Sullivan, 1945; 3 (Reel 149)
  - Officers - Cook, G., 1945; 4 (Reel 149)
  - Officers - Derhammer, R., 1945; 5 (Reel 149)
- 1945: Reel no.3 (Reel 150)
  - Organizers-Cagnon, W., 1945; 1 (Reel 150)
  - Organizers- Hineline, W., 1945; 2 (Reel 150)
  - Organizers - Jackson, R., 1945; 3 (Reel 150)
  - Organizers - Meinz, F., 1945; 4 (Reel 150)
  - Organizers - Parker, O., 1945; 5 (Reel 150)
- 1945: Reel no.4 (Reel 151)
  - Organizers - Patin, A.H, 1945; 1 (Reel 151)
  - Organizers - Segal, H., 1945; 2 (Reel 151)
  - Organizers - Taylor, E., 1945; 3 (Reel 151)
  - Special Organizers - Arsenault, J.L., 1945; 4 (Reel 151)
  - All local Unions-Circular Letters, 1945; 5 (Reel 151)
- 1945: Reel no.5 (Reel 152)
  - Executive Board - Circular Letters, 1945; 1 (Reel 152)
  - Brooks, G.W. - Research Dept. U.S., 1945; 2 (Reel 152)
  - Gramm, S. - Research Dept. U.S., 1945; 3 (Reel 152)
  - Locals - Cambridge, 1945; 4 (Reel 152)
  - Locals-Charleston, 1945; 5 (Reel 152)
- 1945: Reel no.6 (Reel 153)
  - Locals-Charleston, 1945; 1 (Reel 153)
  - Locals -East Side, 1945; 2 (Reel 153)
  - Locals- Great Lakes, 1945; 3 (Reel 153)
  - Locals-Lake St. John, 1945; 4 (Reel 153)
  - Locals - Merrimac, 1945; 5 (Reel 153)
- 1945: Reel no.7 (Reel 154)
  - Local Unions-Merriton, 1945; 1 (Reel 154)
  - Local Unions - North Kansas, 1945; 2 (Reel 154)
  - Local Unions-Paper Box Makers, 1945; 3 (Reel 154)
  - Local Unions - Presswood, 1945; 4 (Reel 154)
- 1945: Reel no.8 (Reel 155)
  - Local Unions-Presswood, 1945; 1 (Reel 155)
  - Local Unions-Savannah, 1945; 2 (Reel 155)
  - LocaI Unions-Thorold, 1945; 3 (Reel 155)
  - Local Unions - Quebec Paper Mill Unions, 1945; 4 (Reel 155)
- 1945: Reel no.9 (Reel 156)
  - Unions-Southern Assoc. of Pulp Ind. Unions, 1945; 1 (Reel 156)
  - Unione-Ind. Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1945; 2 (Reel 156)
  - A. F. of L., 1945; 3 (Reel 156)
  - Governments - Dept. of Labor, 1945; 4 (Reel 156)
  - Governments- M. L. R. E., 1945; 5 (Reel 156)
- 1945: Reel no.10 (Reel 157)
  - Governments- Nat'l & Reg. War Labor Board, 1945; 1 (Reel 157)
  - Governments-War Manpower Comm., 1945; 2 (Reel 157)
  - Companies, 1945; 3 (Reel 157)
  - Companies-Ind. Paper Co., 1945; 4 (Reel 157)
  - Companies - Mersey Paper Co., 1945; 5 (Reel 157)
- 1945: Reel no.11 (Reel 158)
  - Companies-Millet Corp., 1945; 1 (Reel 158)
  - Company Aerostations, 1945; 2 (Reel 158)
- 1946: Reel no.1 (Reel 159)
  - President Secretary Files, 1946; 1 (Reel 159)
  - Officers-Humble, H., 1946; 2 (Reel 159)
  - Officers - Morris, F.W., 1946; 3 (Reel 159)
  - Officers-Sheman, J., 1946; 4 (Reel 159)
  - Officers - Sherman J., 1946; 5 (Reel 159)
- 1946: Reel no.2 (Reel 160)
  - Officers-Stephens, S. A., 1946; 1 (Reel 160)
  - Organizers - Aubuchon, J., 1946; 2 (Reel 160)
  - Organizers - Cianculli, R., 1946; 3 (Reel 160)
  - Organizers - Derhammer, R., 1946; 4 (Reel 160)
  - Organizers - Gordon, L., 1946; 5 (Reel 160)
- 1946: Reel no.3 (Reel 161)
  - Organizers - Gravel, C., 1946; 1 (Reel 161)
  - Organizers - Hetherington, R., 1946; 2 (Reel 161)
  - Organizers - Jackson, R., 1946; 3 (Reel 161)
  - Organizers - Parker, D., 1946; 4 (Reel 161)
  - Organizers - Petretti, J., 1946; 5 (Reel 161)
- 1946: Reel no.4 (Reel 162)
  - Organizers - Phillips, S., 1946; 1 (Reel 162)
  - Organizers - Carter, S., 1946; 2 (Reel 162)
  - Organizers - Van Deusen, F., 1946; 3 (Reel 162)
  - Organizers - Morris, W., 1946; 4 (Reel 162)
  - Special Organizers - Poirier, A., 1946; 5 (Reel 162)
- 1946: Reel no.5 (Reel 163)
  - Special Organizers - Putnam, G.L., 1946; 1 (Reel 163)
  - Circular Letters, 1946; 2 (Reel 163)
  - Canada-Research Dept., 1946; 3 (Reel 163)
- 1946: Reel no.6 (Reel 164)
  - United States-Research Dept., 1946; 1 (Reel 164)
  - United States-Research Dept., 1946; 2 (Reel 164)
  - Local Unions-Bemis, 1946; 3 (Reel 164)
  - Local Unions-Cornwall, 1946; 4 (Reel 164)
  - Local Unions-Detroit, 1946; 5 (Reel 164)
- 1946: Reel no.7 (Reel 165)
  - Local Unions-Dexter, 1946; 1 (Reel 165)
  - Local Unions-Garden City, 1946; 2 (Reel 165)
  - Local Unions-Interstate, 1946; 3 (Reel 165)
  - Local Unions-Manistique, 1946; 4 (Reel 165)
  - Local Unions-Milwaukee, 1946; 5 (Reel 165)
- 1946: Reel no.8 (Reel 166)
  - Local Unions - Milwaukee, 1946; 1 (Reel 166)
  - Local Unions-Panama City, 1946; 2 (Reel 166)
  - Local Unions-Pine Falls, 1946; 3 (Reel 166)
  - Local Unions - St. Mary's, 1946; 4 (Reel 166)
  - Local Unions-Savannah, 1946; 5 (Reel 166)
- 1946: Reel no.9 (Reel 167)
  - Locals-Savannah, 1946; 1 (Reel 167)
  - Locals - Virginia, 1946; 2 (Reel 167)
  - Pulp Sulphite Councils-Pacific Coast, 1946; 3 (Reel 167)
  - Int. Unions - Tex. Workers of America, 1946; 4 (Reel 167)
  - Research-A. F. of L., 1946; 5 (Reel 167)
- 1946: Reel no.10 (Reel 168)
  - Union Label Trades Dept.-A. F. of L., 1946; 1 (Reel 168)
  - Governments-Dept., of Labor, 1946; 2 (Reel 168)
  - General Misc. Files A-Z, 1946; 3 (Reel 168)
  - Companies, 1946; 4 (Reel 168)
  - Companies-Cohoes Env. Co., 1946; 5 (Reel 168)
- 1946: Reel no.11 (Reel 169)
  - Companies-Con. Paper Co., 1946; 1 (Reel 169)
  - Companies-Ontario Paper Co., 1946; 2 (Reel 169)
  - Company Associations, 1946; 3 (Reel 169)
- 1947: Reel no.1 (Reel 170)
  - President Secretary Files, 1947; 1 (Reel 170)
  - Officers - Isaacson, I., 1947; 2 (Reel 170)
  - Officers-Richards, R., 1947; 3 (Reel 170)
  - Officers-Stephens, S., 1947; 4 (Reel 170)
  - 0fficers - Stephens, S., 1947; 5 (Reel 170)
- 1947: Reel no.2 (Reel 171)
  - Officers - Sullivan H.N., 1947; 1 (Reel 171)
  - Organizers - Brodzinski, V., 1947; 2 (Reel 171)
  - Organizers - Cook, G., 1947; 3 (Reel 171)
  - Organizers - Cagnon, W., 1947; 4 (Reel 171)
  - Organizers - Grimaldi, J., 1947; 5 (Reel 171)
- 1947: Reel no.3 (Reel 172)
  - Organizers - Hetherington, R., 1947; 1 (Reel 172)
  - Organizers - Jackson R., 1947; 2 (Reel 172)
  - Organizers - Meinz, E, 1947; 3 (Reel 172)
  - Organizers - Ruddick, D., 1947; 4 (Reel 172)
  - Organizers - Share, C., 1947; 5 (Reel 172)
- 1947: Reel no.4 (Reel 173)
  - Organizers - Simone, J., 1947; 1 (Reel 173)
  - Organizers - Nentz, K., 1947; 2 (Reel 173)
  - Special Organizers - Rickenberg, C., 1947; 3 (Reel 173)
  - Circular Letters, 1947; 4 (Reel 173)
  - Research Dept. of Canada, 1947; 5 (Reel 173)
- 1947: Reel no.5 (Reel 174)
  - Research Dept. of Canada, 1947; 1 (Reel 174)
  - Research Dept. of U.S., 1947; 2 (Reel 174)
  - Local Unions-Bayshore, 1947; 3 (Reel 174)
  - Local Unions-Cleveland, 1947; 4 (Reel 174)
  - Local Unions-Corrugated Fox, 1947; 5 (Reel 174)
- 1947: Reel no.6 (Reel 175)
  - Locals-Corrugated & Fibre Box Makers, 1947; 1 (Reel 175)
  - Locals-Everett, 1947; 2 (Reel 175)
  - Locals-Great Lakes, 1947; 3 (Reel 175)
  - Locals-Lake Champlain, 1947; 4 (Reel 175)
  - Locals-Marimette, 1947; 5 (Reel 175)
- 1947: Reel no.7 (Reel 176)
  - Local Unions-Marion, 1947; 1 (Reel 176)
  - Local Unions-New Toronto, 1947; 2 (Reel 176)
  - Local Unions-Parkersburg, 1947; 3 (Reel 176)
  - Local Unions-Port Huron, 1947; 4 (Reel 176)
  - Local Unions- Reading, 1947; 5 (Reel 176)
- 1947: Reel no.8 (Reel 177)